Guide to the Friendship House Association records, 1904-1992 MS2142
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Friendship House Association records
1904-1992
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Friendship House Association (Washington, D.C.)
MS2142
60 Linear Feet
Collection contains meeting minutes, correspondence, reports, committee records, newspapers, and other materials associated with the work of Friendship House. The records are administrative and financial and describe many of the activities and interests of the organization.
no content
Restrictions on Access
Some records may be restricted.
Acquisition Information
[required]
Historical Note
Friendship House was founded in 1904, and continues today as an active settlement house and neighborhood center in Southeast. It has been described as the oldest and largest settlement house and social service agency in Washington. It was founded with the goal to help those in need to become socially and economically self-reliant. Also Friendship House served as a community center and meeting place for the area. It became in the latter half of the century a conduit to administer social service programs instituted by the city and federal government, and by large private agencies such as United Way. Friendship House had its roots as Rochefort House, begun by a group of young unmarried women who were inspired by the writings of the reformer Jacob Riis. Miss Lydia Burklin began working with the group, and from 1904 until her death in 1964 she devoted all her physical and monetary resources to the project. The house had five rented locations until 1916, when the organization was given deed to 326-328 Virginia Avenue. In 1937 they were able to move to a larger place, their present location. "The Maples" is one of the oldest houses in Washington and is at 619 D Street SE. Generous gifts enabled the organization to add on a theater and annex adjacent property. Miss Burklin lived on the premises for many years and then was given a house nearby. Miss Burklin was able to attract financial help from Washington's businesses and social elite. Friendship House conversely was able to serve this larger constituency by providing an outlet for the charitable volunteer impulses of society women, Congressmen's wives, and also professional social workers, nursery school teachers, musical instructors, etc.
Collection Scope and Content
This collection contains meeting minutes, correspondence, reports, committee records, newspapers, and other materials associated with the work of this organization. The records are administrative and financial and describe many of the activities and interests of Friendship House. The most consistent and comprehensive record of Friendship House's history is in the minutes of the Board of Directors. There are monthly meeting notes from 1904 to 1985. The Friendship House papers cover the years 1904-92.
The papers of Friendship House, a settlement house in southeast Washington DC, were acquired as a part of the Washingtoniana Collection by Gelman Library, Department of Special Collections. The Friendship House papers were arranged and processed under a grant from the National Historic Publications and Records Commission. The grant, entitled "Washington's Hometown History" was granted in the fall of 1990 but actually was not implemented until April of 1991. The one year grant for an archivist, supplies and student assistance, saw the majority of the work completed by June 1992. Because of the volume of the materials to be processed (165 cartons) additional funding was secured from the Mason Fund for completion of the project. The Friendship House papers project was completed in January 1993.
Collection Organization
Organized in seven series: Historical materials, Adminstration, Activities, Financial records, Funding sources, Other organizations, and Oversized records.
Washington (D.C.); Community centers; Social settlements; Friendship House Association (Washington, D.C.); Burklin, Lydia
- Historical Material, 1904-1990; MS2142 Series 1; 2.5 Linear feet (Box 5, Box 4, Box 3, Box 1, Box 2)
  Scope and Contents note
  This series contains photographs, rental agreements, constitutions, bylaws, certificates of incorporation, deeds, factsheets, sketches, correspondence, brochures, maps, postcards, newspaper clippings, histories, reports, fliers, blueprints, publications, floorplans, programs and guest lists. This material dates from 1904 to 1990 with some materials undated. The bulk of the collection material covers 1912 -81.
  - Founding Documents/Legal Documents: Constitution, 06/29/1909 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    General note
  - Founding Documents/Legal Documents: Constitution, 12/31/1912 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Founding Documents/Legal Documents: Constitution, 1912 ca. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Founding Documents/Legal Documents: Constitution - Portion on membership, 1912 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Founding Documents/Legal Documents: Constitution - Reprint of some articles, 1912 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Founding Documents/Legal Documents: Rental Agreement - 324 Virginia Avenue S.E. site, 11/1913 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Founding Documents/Legal Documents: Rental Agreement - Virginia Avenue, 1916 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Founding Documents/Legal Documents: Property Purchase, 12/1916 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Founding Documents/Legal Documents: Deed, 02/1917 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Founding Documents/Legal Documents: Policies of workers, 1920 ca. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Founding Documents/Legal Documents: 324 Virginia Avenue S.E., 10/1923 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Founding Documents/Legal Documents: Deed - Henry Blair and Friendship House, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Founding Documents/Legal Documents: Property papers, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Founding Documents/Legal Documents: Incorporation, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Founding Documents/Legal Documents: Copy of Incorporation, 01/1924 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Founding Documents/Legal Documents: Bylaws, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Founding Documents/Legal Documents: Deed, 01/1926 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Founding Documents/Legal Documents: Correspondence about property, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Founding Documents/Legal Documents: Constitution, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Founding Documents/Legal Documents: Property papers, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Founding Documents/Legal Documents: Tax exemption correspondence, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Founding Documents/Legal Documents: Bylaws, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Founding Documents/Legal Documents: Bylaws - revised, 04/21/1942 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Founding Documents/Legal Documents: Bylaws - proposed amendment, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Founding Documents/Legal Documents: Bylaws, 04/18/1961 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Founding Documents/Legal Documents: Bylaws - revision, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Founding Documents/Legal Documents: Lease for 257 15th Street, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Founding Documents/Legal Documents: Authority for Corporation Account, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Founding Documents/Legal Documents: Bylaws - revision, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Founding Documents/Legal Documents: Bylaws of Car Care, Automotive & Career Training Program, 1970 ca. (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Founding Documents/Legal Documents: Deed, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Founding Documents/Legal Documents: Continuing resolution, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Founding Documents/Legal Documents: Agnes Westlake bequest, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    [see other bequests in Financial Series]
  - Founding Documents/Legal Documents: Bylaws - revision, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Founding Documents/Legal Documents: Bylaws - revision, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Founding Documents/Legal Documents: Property papers, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Founding Documents/Legal Documents: Bylaws - revision, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Founding Documents/Legal Documents: Historic Preservation Covenant, 06/1981 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Historical Material, undated (Box 2)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: Map of Location, 1914 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: Fourteenth Anniversary, 1918 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: Twenty-fifth Anniversary, 1929 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: History of the building "The Maples", 1931 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: 28th Birthday, 1932 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: Newspaper article on "The Maples", 1936 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    This folder contains photographs
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: "New quarters" article, 11/1937 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: Facts on "The Maples", 1930 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: History, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: Verbal sketch, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - . History of the House/Anniversaries: Historical Marker, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: History, 1940 ca. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: Alterations blue prints, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: Fortieth anniversary, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: History, 1909-1949 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: Newspaper photo, 1950 ca. (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: Miss Lydia Burklin's history of Friendship House, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: "A Self Study", 1951 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: Sketches, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: History - Integration, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: History - Integration, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: Fiftieth Anniversary, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: Fiftieth Anniversary, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: Description of "The Maples", 1955 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: History - Integration, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: History - Integration, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: History - "Where Should We Go From Here?", 1958 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: Floor Plan, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: History of "The Maples", 1959 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Historical Material, undated (Box 3)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: History and general overview, 1960 ca. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: Fact sheet, 1960 ca. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: "The Maples" from brochure, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: Clipping on Friendship House, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: Floor Plan, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: Sixtieth Anniversary, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: Landmark in DC, 11/1964 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: Fact sheet, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: "The Maples" by Ruth Ann Overbeck, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: "The Maples" - historical material, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: Protest, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: Exterior photos, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: Map of Area served, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: Locations through the years, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: Fire Bombing, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: Renovations, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: Interior offices, 1970 ca. (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: Sketch, 1970 ca. (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: Comments on programs, 1970 ca. (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: National Register of Historic Places, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: Material on history, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: History of Programs, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: "The Maples" Historic Registration, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: History of "The Maples", 1975 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: "Friendship Communicates", 1975 ca. (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: Programs summary, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: Stabilization of exterior, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: Seventy-fifth anniversary, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: Seventy-fifth anniversary, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: Seventy-fifth anniversary, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: Seventy-fifth anniversary, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: Seventy-fifth anniversary, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: Article on history, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - 1990 annual report (Box 3, Folder 34)
    History of the House/Anniversaries: History from 1990
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: Notes on "The Maples", n.d., undated (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: "The Maples", n.d., undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: Notes on the building of "The Maples", n.d., undated (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: Sketches, n.d., undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - History of the House/Anniversaries: Description in magazine, n.d., undated (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Historical Material, undated (Box 4)
  - Lydia Burklin Personal Papers: Correspondence, 1913 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Lydia Burklin Personal Papers: Correspondence, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Lydia Burklin Personal Papers: Correspondence, 1915 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Lydia Burklin Personal Papers: Correspondence, 1916 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Lydia Burklin Personal Papers: Correspondence, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Lydia Burklin Personal Papers: Correspondence, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Lydia Burklin Personal Papers: Correspondence, 1921 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Lydia Burklin Personal Papers: Correspondence, 1922 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Lydia Burklin Personal Papers: Correspondence, 1924 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Lydia Burklin Personal Papers: Correspondence, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Lydia Burklin Personal Papers: Correspondence, 1932 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Lydia Burklin Personal Papers: Correspondence, 1934 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Lydia Burklin Personal Papers: Correspondence, 1935 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Lydia Burklin Personal Papers: Correspondence, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Lydia Burklin Personal Papers: Correspondence, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Lydia Burklin Personal Papers: Article on Miss Burklin's years at Friendship House, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Lydia Burklin Personal Papers: Correspondence, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Lydia Burklin Personal Papers: Miss Burklin and group, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Lydia Burklin Personal Papers: Correspondence, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Lydia Burklin Personal Papers: Correspondence, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Lydia Burklin Personal Papers: Article on "Capital Careers", 1948 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Lydia Burklin Personal Papers: Correspondence, 1950 ca. (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Lydia Burklin Personal Papers: Miss Burklin and volunteers, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Lydia Burklin Personal Papers: Retirement, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Lydia Burklin Personal Papers: Interview, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Lydia Burklin Personal Papers: Personal history, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Lydia Burklin Personal Papers: "Her Friendship Keeps Growing" Article, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Lydia Burklin Personal Papers: Obituary, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Lydia Burklin Personal Papers: Memorial correspondence, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Lydia Burklin Personal Papers: Memorial gift acknowledgements, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Lydia Burklin Personal Papers: Memorial gift acknowledgements, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Lydia Burklin Personal Papers: Memorial service, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Historical Material, undated (Box 5)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Rochefort Hall Social Center, 1904 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Rochefort House, 1905-1906 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Brochures, 1911-1912 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Brochures, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Brochures, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Brochures, 1917 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Brochures, 1918 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Brochures, 1920 ca. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Postcards, 1921-1923 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Brochures, 1923-1924 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Brochures, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Postcards, 1925 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Brochures, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Postcards, 1930 ca. (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Sketches, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Brochure, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Brochure, 1940 ca. (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Brochure, 1940 ca. (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Brochure, 1940 ca. (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Brochure, 1950 ca. (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Sketch, 1960 ca. (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Brochure - stock offerings, 1962-1964 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Brochures, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Brochure, 1964 ca. (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Brochure, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Brochure, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Brochure - Christmas, 1970 ca. (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Sketch for brochure, 1970 ca. (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Fact sheet, 1970 ca. (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Brochures, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Brochures, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Brochures, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Brochures, 04/1972 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Brochures, 1975 ca. (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Brochures, n.d., undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Brochures, n.d., undated (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Brochures, n.d., undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Historical sketches, undated (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Sketch, n.d., undated (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Fireplace sketch, n.d., undated (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Exterior of house, n.d., undated (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Exterior of house, n.d., undated (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Exterior of house, n.d., undated (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Front door, n.d., undated (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Drawing photo, n.d., undated (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Front door, n.d., undated (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: South East area map, n.d., undated (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Exterior blueprint, n.d., undated (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Brochures/Fliers/Postcards/Sketches: Sketches, n.d., undated (Box 5, Folder 49)
- Administration, 1910-1991; MS2142 Series 2; 18.5 Linear feet (Box 37, Box 38, Box 29, Box 31, Box 32, Box 30, Box 34, Box 33, Box 36, Box 35, Box 23, Box 22, Box 25, Box 24, Box 27, Box 26, Box 20, Box 28, Box 21, Box 16, Box 15, Box 18, Box 17, Box 12, Box 11, Box 14, Box 13, Box 8, Box 7, Box 10, Box 9, Box 6, Box 19)
  This series contains annual reports, monthly reports, newsletters, reports and proposals, committees records, notes, memoranda, correspondence, meeting notices and agenda, meeting minutes, newsletters, publications, organizational charts, and press releases. The materials is dated from 1910 to 1991 with some materials undated. The bulk of the collection materials are dated from 1940 to 1985.
  - Administration, undated (Box 6)
  - Organizational Charts, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Organizational Charts, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Organizational Charts, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Organizational Charts, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Organizational Charts, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Organizational Charts, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Organizational Charts, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Organizational Charts, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Organizational Charts, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Organizational Charts, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Organizational Charts, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Organizational Charts, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Organizational Charts, n.d., undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Annual Report, 12/1910 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Annual Report, 09/1911 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Annual Report, 05/1912 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Annual Report, 10/1917-10/1919 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Annual Report for Year Ending 9/30/1928, 1928-1929 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Annual Report, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Annual Report, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Annual Report, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Annual Report, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Annual Report, 04/1964 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Annual Report, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Annual Report, 04/1972 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Annual Report, 09/1973 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Annual Report, 09/1976 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Annual Report, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Annual Report, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Annual Report, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Administration, undated (Box 7)
  - Monthly Report, 02/1966 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Monthly Report, 07/1967 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Monthly Reports, 12/1967 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Monthly Reports, 07/1968 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Monthly Report, 03/1968 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Monthly Report, 06/1968 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Monthly Report, 07/1968 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Monthly Reports, 12/1968 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Monthly Reports (Capper Unit), 06/1969 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Monthly Reports, 02/1969 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Monthly Report, 02/1969 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Monthly Report, 03/1969 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Monthly Report, 04/1969 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Monthly Report, 05/1969 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Monthly Report, 06/1969 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Monthly Report, 07/1969 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Monthly Report, 08/1969 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Monthly Report, 09/1969 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Monthly Report, 10/1969 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Monthly Report, 11/1969 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Monthly Report, 12/1969 (Box 7, Folder 21)